Guide to the Sam di Bonaventura papers, 1900-1998
George Mason University Libraries
- Dr. Sam di Bonaventura papers
  - Berlioz A-N [1965-1976-] (Box 21)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Bibliography (EMPTY), 2.Biography, 3.Cantata, 4.Choral Misc., 5.Complete Works, 6.Concerto, 7.Instrumental Misc., 8.Letters, 9.Literary, 10.March, 11.Mass, 12.Misc. Date(s) of materials: 1965, 1969, 1972, 1975, 1976-
  - Berlioz O-Z [1943-1976] (Box 21)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Opera, 2.Oratorio, 3.Orchestral Misc., 4.Overture, 5.Song, 6.Style, 7.Te Deum Dates of materials: 1943, 1960, 1973, 1976-
  - Berlioz Symphony [1966-1984-] (Box 21)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Program Notes Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Fantastique, 3.Funebre, 4.Harold, 5.Romeo and Juliet Dates of materials: 1966, 1975, 1984-
  - Bernstein [1971-1982] (Box 22)
    Content: Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1.Aesthetics, 2.Ballet, 3.Bibliography (EMPTY), 4.Biography, 5.Complete Works, 6.Incidental Music, 7.Literary, 8.Mass, 9.Misc., 10.Opera, 11.Orchestral Misc., 12.Overture, 13.Piano Misc., 14.Psalm, 15.Serenade, 16.Sonata, 17.Song, 18.Style (EMPTY), 19.Symphony Dates of materials: 1971,1975, 1982-
  - Biber/Binchois [1971-1974-] (Box 22)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Biber, Franz (1644-1704), 2.Binchois, Gilles (c.1400-60) Dates of materials: 1971, 1974-
  - Bizet [1905-1985] (Box 22)
    Content: Articles Headings: 1.Unlabeled (Bizet Misc.-Pearl Fishers, Carmen, Symphony), 2.Unlabeled (Carmen) Date(s) of materials: 1905, 1941, 1965, 1977, 1985-
  - Blacher/Blackwood/Boccherini [1968-1978-] (Box 22)
    Content: Articles, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Blacher, 2.Blackwood, 3.Boccherini Dates of materials: 1968, 1976, 1978-
  - Bloch [1966-1979-] (Box 22)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Biography, 2.Concerto, 3.Instrumental Misc., 4.Misc., 5.Opera, 6.Piano Misc., 7.Quartet, 8.Quintet, 9.Rhapsody, 10.Service, 11.Sonata, 12.Style, 13.Suite, 14.Symphony, 15.Tone Poem Dates of materials: 1966, 1979-
  - Bononcini, G.M. 1962 (Box 23)
    Content: Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Bibliography, 2.Biography, 3.Canon, 4.Complete Works, 5.Dance, 6.Misc., 7.Sonata, 8.Unlabeled: Bononcini-Selected works Dates of materials: 1962
  - Boulez/Brown [1962-1981-] (Box 23)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1.Boulez, 2.Brown Dates of materials: 1968, 1971, 1981-
  - Brahms A-N [1970-1989-] (Box 23)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Ballade (EMPTY), 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Cantata (EMPTY), 5.Chamber Misc., 6.Complete Works, 7.Dance, 8.Fantasia (EMPTY), 9.Fugue, 10.Intermezzo, 11.Letters, 12.Literary, 13.Misc., 14.Motet Dates of materials: 1970, 1973, 1989-
  - Brahms Choral [1974-1978] (Box 23)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Arrangement, 2.Ballad (EMPTY), 3.Canon, 4.Choral Music, 5.Psalm (EMPTY), 6.Quartet, 7.Requiem, 8.Rhapsody, 9.Rinaldo (EMPTY), 10.Romance, 11.Sacred Misc., 12.Schicksalslied, 13.Tafellied, 14.Triumphlied, 15.Zigeunerlied Dates of materials: 1974, 1978
  - Brahms Concerto [1971-1987] (Box 23)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Piano No.1, 3.Piano No.2, 4.Violin, 5.Violin-Cello Date(s) of materials: 1971, 1973, 1975, 1978, 1987-
  - Brahms O-Sc [1944-1972] (Box 24)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Charts Headings: 1.Orchestral Music, 2.Organ Misc. (EMPTY), 3.Overture, 4.Piano Misc., 5.Quartet, 6.Quintet, 7.Requiem, 8.Rhapsody, 9.Scherzo (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1944, 1964, 1968, 1972-
  - Brahms Se-Z [1969-1988] (Box 24)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Serenade, 2.Sextet (EMPTY), 3.Sonata, 4.Song, 5.Style, 6.Transcription, 7.Trio, 8.Variation Date(s) of materials: 1969, 1978, 1988-
  - Brahms Symphony I [1971-1987] (Box 24)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Misc., 2.No.1, 3.No.2 Date(s) of materials: 1971, 1975, 1976, 1987-
  - Brahms Symphony II [1971-1979] (Box 24)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.No. 3, 2.No. 4 Date(s) of materials: 1971, 1972, 1978, 1979-
  - Britten (Opera) [1962-1985] (Box 25)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers, Concert Papers Headings: 1.Beggar's Opera, 2.Budd, Billy, 3.Burning Furnace, 4.Curlew River, 5.Gloriana, 6.Grimes, Peter, 7.Herring, Albert, 8.Let's Make Opera, 9.Midsummer, 10.Noye's Fludde, 11.Opera Misc., 12.Prince of Pagodas (EMPTY), 13.Prodigal Son, 14.Rape of Lucretia, 15.Unlabled (Turn [of the Screw]) Dates of materials: 1962, 1971, 1985
  - Britten I [1976-1989] (Box 25)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Bibliography, 3.Biography, 4.Cantata, 5.Carol, 6.Chamber Misc. (EMPTY), 7.Choral Misc., 8.Complete Works, 9.Concerto, 10.Film Music, 11.Hymn, 12.Instrumental Music, 13.Letters (EMPTY), 14.Literary (EMPTY), 15.Mass, 16.Misc., 17.Nocturne, 18.Orchestral Music, 19.Prelude (EMPTY), 20.Psalm (EMPTY), 21.Quartet (EMPTY) Date(s) of materials: 1976, 1988, 1989-
  - Britten II [1960-1987] (Box 25)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Requiem, 2.Sonata, 3.Song, 4.Style, 5.Suite, 6.Symphony, 7.Te Deum, 8.Transcription, 9.Variation Dates of materials: 1960, 1966, 1978, 1987-
  - Bruckner [1967-1972] (Box 25)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Bibliography (EMPTY), 2.Biography, 3.Choral Misc., 4.Complete Works, 5.Intermezzo, 6.Letters, 7.Magnificat (EMPTY), 8.Mass, 9.Misc., 10.Motet (EMPTY), 11.Organ Misc. (EMPTY), 12.Overture, 13.Psalm (EMPTY), 14.Quartet, 15.Quintet, 16.Song (EMPTY), 17.Style, 18.Te Deum Dates of materials: 1967, 1972-
  - Bruckner Symphony I [1968-1985] (Box 26)
    Content: Articles Headings: 1.Misc., 2.No. I, 3.No. II, 4.No. III, 5.Unlabeled (No. IV), 6.No. V Date(s) of materials: 1968, 1971, 1979, 1985-
  - Bruckner Symphony II [1962-1986] (Box 26)
    Content: Articles, Notes Headings: 1.No. VI, 2.No. VII, 3.No. VIII, 4.No. IX Date(s) of materials: 1962, 1976, 1982, 1986-
  - Buonamente (1626-) (Box 26)
    Content: Musical Scores of sonatas by composer Buonamente Headings: None. Fills a 1" binder. Dates of materials: 1626-
  - Caccini/Carissimi/Corelli 1972 (Box 26)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Caccini, Giulio (c.1560-1618), 2.Carissimi, Giacomo (1605-74), 3.Corelli, Arcangelo (1653-1713) Dates of materials: 1972
  - Cage [1966-1980] (Box 26)
    Content: Articles, Notes Headings: None. Misc. information on composer John Cage. Fills a 1" binder. Date(s) of materials: 1966, 1977, 1980-
  - Carter [1968-1988] (Box 27)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Ballet (EMPTY), 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Canon (EMPTY), 5.Chamb. Misc., 6.Choral Misc., 7.Comp. Works, 8.Concerto, 9.Discography, 10.Etude, 11.Fantasia, 12.Incidental Music (EMPTY), 13.Instrumental, 14.Letters (EMPTY), 15.Literary, 16.Madrigal, 17.Misc., 18.Opera (EMPTY), 19.Oratorio (EMPTY), 20.Orch. Misc. (EMPTY), 21.Overture, 22.Quartet, 23.Quintet, 24.Sonata, 25.Song, 26.Style, 27.Suite, 28.Symphony, 29.Variation, 30.Vocal Misc. Dates of materials: 1968, 1988
  - Chamber Music Composers M-S 1982 (Box 27)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Mendelssohn, 2.Milhaud, 3.Nardini, 4.Paradisi, 5.Parry, 6.Pergolesi, 7.Piston, 8.Poulenc, 9.Prokofiev, 10.Pugnani, 11.Purcell, 12.Ravel, 13.Reger, 14.Rimsky, 15.Rosenmueller, 16.Roussel, 17.Rubenstein, A., 18.Saint-Saens, 19.Sammartini, 20.Schobert, 21.Schoenberg, 22.Schubert, 23.Schuman [William] Date(s) of materials: 1982
  - Chamber Music Literature I 1974 (Box 27)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers, Charts Headings: 1.Arensky, 2.J.C. Bach, 3.C.P.E. Bach, 4.J.S. Bach, 5.W.F. Bach, 6.Bartok, 7.Beethoven, 8.Berg, 9.Biber, 10.Boccherini, 11.Borodin Dates of materials: 1974
  - Chamber Music Literature II 1974 (Box 27)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Brahms, 2.Cazzati, 3.Clementi, 4.Cooper, 5.Corelli, 6.Couperin, 7.Debussy, 8.Dittersdorf, 9.Dvorak, 10.Fasch, 11.Faure, 12.Franck, 13.Gabrielli, 14.Gade, 15.Geminiani, 16.Gibbons, 17.Glazunov, 18.Gluck, 19.Handel, 20.Harris, 21.Hindemith, 22.Honegger, 23.d'Indy, 24.Janacek, 25.Kodaly, 26.Krenek, 27.Lalo, 28.Lawes, W., 29.Leclair, 30.Legrenzi, 31.Locatelli, 32.Loeillet, 33.MacKenzie, 34.Malipiero, 35.Marini, 36.Martinu Dates of materials: 1974
  - Chamber Music Literature III 1982 (Box 27)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Haydn, 2.Mozart Date(s) of materials: 1982
  - Chamber Music Literature IV 1982 (Box 28)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Schumann, 2.Shostakovich, 3.Smetana, 4.Spohr, 5.Stamitz, 6.Stanford, 7.Stravinsky, 8.Tartini, 9.Tchaikovsky, 10.Telemann, 11.Torelli, 12.Vanhall, 13.Veracini, 14.Villa-Lobos, 15.Viotti, 16.Vitali, 17.Vivaldi, 18.Webern, 19.Misc. Dates of materials: 1982
  - Chausson/Chavez [1966-1981] (Box 28)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Chausson, Ernest (1855-99), 2.Unlabeled (Chavez, Carlos (1899-1978)) Dates of materials: 1966, 1970, 1973, 1981
  - Cheslock [1968-1982-] (Box 28)
    Content: Dissertation (1979), Notes, Articles Headings: None. Fills a 1" binder Date(s) of materials: 1968, 1979, 1982-
  - China I 1975 (Box 28)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers, Illustrations, Class Outlines Headings: 1.Outlines, 2.History, 3.Culture, 4.Music, 5.Theory, 6.Notation, 7.Instruments, 8.Performance Practice, 9.Art, 10.Theatre, Dates of materials: 1975
  - China II [1962-1969-] (Box 28)
    Content: Articles, Notes Headings: 1.China Date(s) of materials: 1962, 1969-
  - China III (Box 29)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1.Geography, 2.Astrology, 3.History, 4.Outline, 5.Society, 6.Instruments, 7.Literature, 8.Theory, 9.Notation, 10.Bach:Variation, 11.Music, 12.Theater Date(s) of materials: ?
  - Chopin I [1944-1983-] (Box 29)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers, Illustrations Headings: 1.Bibliography (EMPTY), 2.Biography, 3.Ballade, 4.Barcarolle, 5.Berceuse, 6.Complete Works, 7.Concerto No. 1, 8.Concerto No. 2, 9.Dance Misc., 10.Etude, 11.Fantasia, 12.Fugue (EMPTY), 13.Impromptu Date(s) of materials: 1944, 1968, 1978, 1983-
  - Chopin II [1902-1992] (Box 29)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Letters, 2.March, 3.Mazurka, 4.Misc., 5.Nocturne, 6.Piano Misc., 7.Polonaise, 8.Prelude, 9.Rondo, 10.Scherzo, 11.Sonata:Cello, 12.Sonata No. 1, 13.Sonata No. 2, 14.Sonata No. 3, 15.Song, 16.Style, 17.Trio (EMPTY), 18.Variation, 19.Waltz Dates of materials: 1902, 1959, 1964, 1967, 1979, 1992-
  - Choral Lists 1965 (Box 29)
    Content: Lists, Articles Headings: None. Content fill a 2" binder Date(s) of materials: 1965
  - Classical 8 (Box 29)
    Content: Notes Headings: 1.Classicism, 2.Musical Characteristics, 3.Symphony, 4.Concerto, 5.Sinfonie Concertante, 6.Serenade, 7.Chamber Music, 8.Sonata, 9.Sacred Music, 10.Piano Date(s) of materials: ?
  - Classical 9 1980 (Box 29)
    Content: Notes Headings: 1.Music, 2.Mannheim, 3.Sonata, 4.Opera, 5.Concerto, 6.Symphony, 7.Serenade, 8.Performance Practice, 9.Term Papers Dates of materials: 1980
  - Classical 10 1975 (Box 30)
    Content: Notes Headings: 1.Classical, 2.Classical Review, 3.Chamber Music, 4.Cristofori, 5.Concerto, 6.Form, 7.Serenade, 8.Symphony, 9.Opera, 10.Opera: Seria vs. Buffa, 11.Mozart: Opera, 12.Pergolesi: Opera Dates of materials: 1975
  - Classical 11 (C-O) 1969 (Box 30)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Cantata, 2.Chamber (EMPTY), 3.Choral, 4.Compositional Practice, 5.Concerto, 6.Historical, 7.Instrumental, 8.Keyboard, 9.Literary (EMPTY), 10.Mass (EMPTY), 11.Misc., 12.Notation, 13.Opera, 14.Oratorio (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1969
  - Claudin I 1959 (Box 30)
    Content: Musical Scores, Notes Headings: 1.Biography (EMPTY), 2.Complete Works, 3.Mass Misc., 4.Missa AB Initio, 5.Missa AD Placitum, 6.Missa Domine Quis, 7.Missa Domini Est Terra, 8.Missa Nove Lectionum, 9.Missa Philomena, 10.Missa Plurium Modulorum Dates of materials: 1959
  - Claudin II 1959 (Box 30)
    Content: Musical Scores, Notes Headings: 1.Missa Plurium Motetorum, 2.Missa Quare Tremuerunt, 3.Missa Requiem, 4.Missa Tota Pulchra Es, 5.Missa Voulant Honneur, 6.Motet, 7.Song, 8.Works for Parody (EMPTY), 9.Style Dates of materials: 1959
  - Composers A-Albo [1946-1985-] (Box 31)
    Contents: Musical Scores, Articles Headings: 1.dalAbaco, E.F., 2.Abbatini, 3.Acourt, 4.Adam, 5.Adam de la Halle, 6.Adam de St. Victor, 7.Unlabeled:Adam, A, 8.Adams, Claus, 9.Adams, D 10.Adams, J., 11.Addinsell, 12.Adler, S., 13.Adolphe, 14.dAgincour, 15.Agricola, A (EMPTY), 16.Agricola, J.F. (EMPTY), 17.Aho, 18.Ahrendt, K., 19.Aichinger, 20.Ainsworth, 21.Aitken, 22.Akutagawa 23.Alain, 24.Albeniz, 25.DAlbert, 26.Albert, H., 27.Albert, P., 28.Albicastro, 29.Albinoni, T.G. Dates of materials: 1946, 1985-
  - Composers Albr-Ap [1967-1983] (Box 31)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Albrechtsberger, 2.Albrici, 3.Albright, 4.Alcaraz, 5.Aldrich, D., 6.Aldrich, H., 7.Alexander, 8.Alfano, 9.Alford, 10.Alfven, 11.Alison, R., 12.Alix, 13.Alkan, 14.Allanbrook, 15.Allegri, 16.Almeida, 17.Altenburg, 18.DAlvimare, 19.Alwyn, 20.Ames, R., 21.Ammerbach, 22.Amram, 23.Amy, 24.Ana, 25.Anchieta, 26.Anderberg, 27.Anderson, L., 28.Anderson, T.J., 29.Andreae, 30.Andrews, R., 31.Andriessen, 32.Andrieu, 33.Andrix, 34.Anerio, F., 35.Anerio, G.F., 36.Anet, 37.Anfossi, 38.dAnglebert, 39.Anhalt, 40.Antes, 41.Antheil, 42.Anthonello, 43.Antico, 44.Antonii, 45.Antoniu, 46.Antonolini, 47.Applebaum, 48.Appleton Dates of materials: 1967,1972,1983-
  - Composers Ar-Az [1953-1962-] (Box 31)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Araujo (EMPTY), 2.Arcadelt, 3.Ardevol, 4.Arel, 5.Argento, 6.Arlan, D., 7.Arnatt, 8.Arne, 9.Arnell, 10.Arnldus de Bruck, 11.Arnold de Lantins, 12.Arnold, Malcolm, 13.Arnold, Maurice, 14.Arnold, S., 15.Arriaga, 16.Unlabeled:Arrigo, 17.Arthur, J., 18.Ascencio, 19.Ascher, 20.Ascue, 21.Ashley, 22.Ashton, W., 23.Asola, 24.Assandra (EMPTY), 25.Astonia, 26.Aston, H., 27.Attaignant, 28.Atterberg, 29.Attey, 30.Attwood (EMPTY), 31.Aubart, 32.Auber, 33.Auric, 34.Austin, 35.dAuvergne, 36.Aux Costeau, 37.Avison, 38.Avni, 39.Avshalomov, 40.Ayres, 41.Axelrod Dates of materials: 1953,1962-
  - Composers Ba-Bar [1967-1976] (Box 31)
    Contents: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Babbit, 2.Bach, J., 3.Bacheler, D., 4.Bachmann, 5.Bacon, 6.Badarzewska, 7.Badings, 8.Baeck, 9.Baird, 10.Baj (EMPTY), 11.Baker, C, 12.Baker, R., 13.Balada, 14.Balakirev, 15.Balassa, 16.Bales, 17.Balfe, 18.Ballantine, 19.Balls, 20.Baltzer, 21.Bamert, 22.Barati, 23.Barbaud, 24.Barbe, 25.Barbier, 26.Barbirolli, 27.Barboteli, 28.Bark, 29.Barker, 30.Barlow, 31.Barney, Joseph, 32.Barnes, B., 33.Baronnet, 34.Barr, M. 35.Barraque, 36.Barre, 37.Bartholus, 38.Bartolino, 39.Bartolomeus, 40.Bartolozzi, 41.Bartolucci, 42.Barton, A., 43.Barton, M. Dates of materials: 1967, 1976-
  - Composers Bas-Bep [1952-1991-] (Box 32)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Basart, 2.Basiron, 3.Bassett, 4.Bassevi (EMPTY), 5.Bateson, 6.Batten, 7.Baumgartner, 8.Bak, 9.Bayer, 10.Bayle, 11.Bazelon, 12.Beale, 13.Beaujoyeaulx, B, 14.Beck, C., 15.Beck, F., 16.Becker, 17.Beckwith, J., 18.Beckwith, J.C., 19.Bedford, 20.Beesson, 21.Behrman, 22.Belasco, 23.Belcher, 24.Bellak, 25.Bellamy, 26.BellHaver, 27.Bellman, 28.Bencini, 29.Benda, F., 30.Benda, G., 31.Benet, 32.Benevoli, 33.Ben- Haim, 34.Benjamin, 35.Bennet, John, 36.Bennett, B., 37.Bennett, R. Rod., 38.Bennett, R. Rus., 39.Bennett, W. S., 40.Benson, A.C., 41.Benson, W., 42.Bentzon, Niels V., 43.Benvenuti Dates of materials: 1953, 1970, 1982, 1991-
  - Composers Be-Berl [1968-1998] (Box 32)
    Content: Notes, Scholarly Papers, Articles, Program Notes Headings: 1.Beethoven (Piano No. 3; Piano No. 4; Piano No. 5; Violin Concerto, 6.Beethoven: Consecration; Prometheus; Egmont; Leonore No. 3; Romance No. 2; Symph. No. 1; Symph. No. 6; Symph. No. 7; Symph. No. 8; Symph. No. 9), 2.Berg, 3.Berlioz (Damn. of Faust; Overture: Roman Carnival; Symph. Fantastique) Dates of materials: 1968, 1970, 1979, 1994, 1995, 1996, 1998
  - Composers Ber-Bir [1971-1981] (Box 32)
    Content: Articles, Musical Scores, Notes Headings: 1.Berchem, 2.Berger, A., 3.Berger, T., 4.Bergman, Erik, 5.Bergsma, 6.Bergson, M., 7.Berio, 8.Berkeley, 9.Berkowitz, 10.Berlinsky, 11.Bermudo, 12.Bernabei, 13.Bernal-Jimenez, 14.Bernard, 15.Bernardi, 16.Bernart Ventadorn, 17.Bernasconi, 18.Bernhard, 19.Bernier, 20.Bertin, 21.Bertoni, 22.Bertrand, 23.Berwald, 24.Bettinelli, 25.Beyer, 26.Bialas, 27.Bibalo, 28.Billings, 29.Binkerd, 30.Bird, 31.Birtwistle Dates of materials: 1971, 1976, 1981
  - Composers Bis-Boi [1953-1982] (Box 32)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Biscardi, 2.Bishop, 3.Bissell, 4.Bittner, 5.Blackford, 6.Bladen, 7.Blaise, 8.Blake, 9.Blake, D., 10.Blake, E..11.Blake,R., 12.Blakey, 13.Blanchard, 14.Bland, 15.Blank, 16.Blanks, 17.Blavet, 18.Bleyer, 19.Bliss, 20.Blitheman, 21.Blitzstein, 22.Bloch, A., 23.Blomdahl, 24.Blow, 25.Blumenfeld, 26.Boatrite, 27.Boatwright, 28.Bodenschatz, 29.Boeddecker, 30.Boehm, G., 31.Boehm, K., 32.Boehm, T., 33.Boehmer, 34.Boesset, 35.Bohlen, 36.Boieldieu, 37.Boismortier, 38.Boito Dates of materials: 1953, 1962, 1964, 1967, 1972, 1980, 1982
  - Composers Bol-Bou [1966-1981] (Box 33)
    Content: Articles, Program Notes, Concert Programs, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Bolcom, 2.Boldemann, 3.Bomtempo, 4.Bonde, 5.Bono, 6.Bononcini, A.M., 7.Bononcini, G.B., 8.Bonporti, 9.Boone, 10.Boretti, 11.Borghi, 12.Borlet, 13.Borodin, 14.Bortnianski (EMPTY), 15.Boscovitch, 16.Bossi, 17.Bossinensis, 18.Bottesini, 19.Bottje, 20.Bottrigari, 21.Boumgartner, 22.Bourgeois (EMPTY), 23.Bousset (EMPTY), 24.Boutilier, 25.Bouvard (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1966, 1967, 1969, 1971, 1977, 1978, 1981
  - Composers Bow-Bro [1953-1982] (Box 33)
    Content: Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Program Notes Headings: 1.Bowen, 2.Bowles, 3.Boyce, 4.Boyton, 5.Bozay, 6.Bozza, 7.Brackman, 8.Bradbery, 9.Brade (EMPTY), 10.Braein, 11.Branco, 12.Brandon, 13.Brandt, C., 14.Brant, 15.Brassin, 16.Braunlich, 17.Bray, John, 18.Brel, Jacque, 19.Bremner, 20.Brescianello, 21.Bresgen, 22.Brenick, 23.Breval, 24.Brewer, 25.Brian, 26.Bridge, 27.Brindle, 28.Brings, 29.Briquet, 30.Bristow, 31.Unlabeled (Brixi), 32.Brocus, 33.Broderip, 34.Broman, 35.Brome, 36.Brooke, 37.Brooks, 38.Brooks, R.J., 39.Brott, 40.Brouwer, 41.Brown, R., 42.Browne Dates of materials: 1953, 1960, 1969, 1976, 1982
  - Composers Bru-Bur [1952-1989] (Box 33)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Concert Programs, Program Notes Headings: 1.Brubeck, D., 2.Brubeck, H., 3.Bruch, 4.Bruck, 5.Brudieu, 6.Bruhns, 7.Brulo, 8.Brumel, 9.Bruneau, 10.Brunetti, 11.Brunswick, 12.Bryant, 13.Bubalo, 14.Bucci, 15.Buchner (EMPTY), 16.Bucht, 17.Buck, 18.Budd, 19.Bull, 20.Bullock, 21.Burge, 22.Burgess, 23.Burian, 24.Burkhard, F., 25.Burkhard, P., 26.Burkhard, W., 27.Burleigh, 28.Burt, 29.Burton, J., 30.Burton, S. Dates of materials: 1952, 1962, 1968, 1970, 1978, 1989
  - Composers B-S 1953 (Box 33)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Articles Headings: 1.Bach, 2.Beethoven, 3.Chopin, 4.Handel, 5.Mozart, 6.Prokofiev, 7.Scriabin, 8.Schumann Dates of materials: 1953
  - Composers Bus-Bz [1962-1982] (Box 34)
    Content: Articles, Musical Scores, Notes, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Bush, 2.Busnois, 3.Unlabeled (Busoni), 4.Bussotti, 5.Butterly, 6.Buttstedt (EMPTY), 7.Buxtehude, 8.Byrd, J., 9.Byrd, W., 10.Byrne Dates of materials: 1962, 1963, 1976, 1982
  - Composers Ca-Cap [1953-1990] (Box 34)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Cabanilles, 2.Cabezon, 3.Caccini, 4.Caceres, 5.Cadeac, 6.Cadman, 7.Calabro, 8.Callcot, J., 9.Caldara, 10.Call, 11.Callaway, 12.Caltabiano, 13.Calvisius, 14.Cambefort (EMPTY), 15.Cambert, 16.Camidge, 17.Camilleri, 18.Campion, 19.Campioni, 20.Campos-Parsi, 21.Campra, 22.Camps, 23.Cannabich, 24.Canning, 25.Canteloube, 26.Capirola, 27.Capua Dates of materials: 1953, 1973, 1980, 1984, 1990
  - Composers Car [1953-1981] (Box 34)
    Content: Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Notes Headings: 1.Cara, 2.Carden, 3.Cardoso, 4.Cardot, 5.Care, 6.Carey, H., 7.Carillo, 8.Carisi, 9.Carleton, N., 10.Carlid, 11.Carlstedt, 12.Carlos, 13.Carmen, 14.Carmines, 15.Caron, P., 16.Carpenter, J.A., 17.Carpentras, 18.Carr, B., 19.Carriere, 20.Carrillo, 21.Carter, J., 22.Carter, T., 23.Carulli, 24.Carvalho, 25.Carver, R. Dates of materials: 1953, 1966, 1973, 1976, 1981
  - Composers Cas-Caz [1963-1982] (Box 34)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Casadesus, R., 2.Casals, 3.Casella, 4.Castaldo, 5.Castello, 6.Castelnuovo- Ted., 7.Catiglioni, 8.Castro, J.J., 9.Catalani, 10.Cavaccio, 11.Cavalieri, 12.Cavalli, 13.Cavazzoni, 14.Cazden, 15.Cazzati Dates of materials: 1963, 1966, 1973, 1982
  - Composers Ce-Cha [1948-1982] (Box 35)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Concert Programs, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Cedronio, 2.Cerha, 3.Cernohorsky, 4.Certon, 5.Cervetti, 6.Cesano (EMPTY), 7.Cesaris, 8.Cesti, 9.Chabrier, 10.Chadabe, 11.Chadwick, 12.Chagrin, 13.Chaikovsky, 14.Challoner, 15.Chambonnieres, 16.Chapi, 17.Chapin, 18.Charit, 19.Charpentier, G., 20.Charpentier, J., 21.Charpentier, M.A., 22.Chatman, 23.Chaudoir, 24.Chauls, 25.Chaumont, 26.Chaynes Dates of materials: 1948, 1969, 1975, 1977, 1979, 1982
  - Composers Che-Cla [1953-1990] (Box 35)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Cheney, 2.Cherubini, 3.Chetwood, 4.Chiari, 5.Chilcot, 6.Child, W., 7.Childs, 8.Cibber, C., 9.Cibber, T., 10.Chilliwack, 11.Christou, 12.Chorley, 13.Ciconia, 14.Cikker, 15.Cilea, 16.Cima, 17.Cimara, 18.Cimarosa, 19.Cimello, 20.Clair, 21.Clark, R.K., 22.Clark, S., 23.Clark, H.L., 24.Clark, J., 25.Clasing Dates of materials: 1953, 1963, 1972, 1982, 1986, 1990
  - Composers Cle-Colg [1953-1991] (Box 35)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Articles Headings: 1.Clemens, 2.Clementi, 3.Clementi, A., 4.Clerambolt, 5.Clough-Leighter, 6.Clouser, 7.Coates, 8.Cocchi, 9.Coccia (EMPTY), 10.Coclico, 11.Codax, 12.Coe, 13.Coelho, 14.Coerne, 15.Coffey, 16.Cogan, R, 17.Cohen, F., 18.Cohn, A., 19.Cohn, J., 20.Coker, 21.Colasse, 22.Coleridge-Tay, 23.Colgrass Dates of materials: 1953, 1966, 1976, 1985, 1989, 1991
  - Composers Colm-Cop [1953-1979] (Box 35)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Colman, 2.Colonna, 3.Unlabeled (Colombi, G.), 4.Compere, 5.Cone, E.T., 6.Connelly, 7.Conradin, 8.Conseil, 9.Consoli, 10.Constant, 11.Constantinescu, 12.Constantinides, 13.Conti, 14.Contractus, 15.Converse, 16.Cooke, A., 17.Cooke, B., 18.Cooke, E., 19.Cooke, T., 20.Cooley, J., 21.Cooper, 22.Coots, 23.Cope Dates of materials: 1953, 1962, 1979
  - Composers Cor-Cz [1960-1992] (Box 36)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Cordero, 2.Cordier, 3.Corea, 4.Corigliano, 5.Corkine, 6.Cornelius, 7.Corner, 8.Cornish, 9.Cornet, 10.Corrette, 11.Corsi, 12.Corteccia, 13.Corwell, 14.Costeley, 15.Continesco, 16.Cosyn, 17.Cotel, 18.Coulthard, 19.Cox, R., 20.Coyner, 21.Crawford, J., 22.Crequillon, 23.Crema, 24.Crispinus, 25.Crivelli, 26.Croce, 27.Croft, W., 28.Crosse, 29.Crotch, 30.Cui, 31.Cumming, 32.Curran, 33.Custer, 34.Cutting, 35.Cyr, 36.Czerny, 37.Czyz Dates of materials: 1960, 1974, 1989, 1992
  - Composers Da-Dela [1953-1985] (Box 36)